(Amy:)Better?
(Amy:)Baguettes.
Yes, I like baguettes.
(Sheldon:)What exactly are you doing?
(Amy:)Determining baseline fear levels
in capuchin monkeys
(Amy:)by measuring their response
to visual stimuli.
(Sheldon:)So, goofing off.
(Sheldon:)As I was saying, I'm done with work
and Leonard's not.
(Sheldon:)So good news,
you get to take me home.
(Sheldon:)Play your cards right,
I'll let you drive me
(Sheldon:)past the lot
where the buses park at night.
(Amy:)I can't leave now, Sheldon.
I'm very busy.
(Amy:)Besides, why would I want to do you
a favour
(Amy:)after the way you treated me
in the cafeteria?
Image number tour: boa constrictor.
(Sheldon:)What on earth are you talking about?
My behavior in the cafeteria
was delightful.
(Sheldon:)Maybe your friend Gunderson needs
to head over to IKEA
and assemble a sense of humor.
(Amy:)You embarrassed me in front of
my colleagues on my first day here.
Image number five:
kitten in a teacup.